

# FAWAZ SIDHIK

### **SUMMARY**

More than 7 years of professional experience in procurement, logistics operations, marketing and sales in the UAE. I believe my exposure to various fields makes me a competitive candidate for any organization looking to hire the best.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **OPERATIONS AND PROCUREMENT (AUG 2016 - SEP 2020)**

#### Focus Building Material - Dubai

- Leading the team at various areas in retail operations and proactively allocating manpower to meet customer expectations
- Mentoring new joiners for their product knowledge and to bring out their potential in delivering exceptional customer service
- Managing the team with sales and merchandise requests
- Agile in familiarizing the up and coming building materials
- Procuring brands such as Maestro from Italy, Grohe from Germany, RAK Ceramics from Ras Al Khaimah and various other international and local brands
- Identifying current and future customer requirements by building rapport and providing occasional services in order to maintain their loyalty to the brand.
- Adapting to flexible schedules to cover work hours based on business needs and other adhoc requirements
- Conducting various HR functions such as interviewing, appraisals and performance reviews

### LOGISTICS CO-ORDINATOR (AUG 2015 - JUN 2016)

# Khalfan Al Shayer General Trading - UAE

- Negotiating with suppliers and ensure to receive products at best prices in the market
- Responsible for tracking products from supplier to warehouse and setting up the stocks appropriately
- Ensuring each area of store is stocked and ensure proper housekeeping is carried out
- Making sure customers find everything they need in the right place
- Replenishing product display stocks in line with company plans.
- Monitoring stock levels and reviewing product performance in order to identify current and future business opportunities
- Dispatching products to customers, tracking cargo and updating the customers about deliveries in a timely manner.

## ASSISTANT STORE MANAGER (MAY 2013 - JUN 2015)

## Genova Trading - UAE

- Controlling stock and inventories to assure they are up to the standard and meets customer requirements and demands
- Dealing with customer complaints and thoroughly following up until the problem is resolved.
- Promoting sales by assisting staffs with merchandising products to all customers
- Pricing products according to current market value and in a strategic way that appeals to customers and gain revenue

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelors of Business Administrations - City College Ajman

#### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- Operations and Administration
- Corporate Communication Skills
- People Skilled and Proactiveness
- Leadership and Empathetic Natured
- Planning and Organizational Skills

# **INTERESTS**

- Tech Enthusiast
- Sports
- Gaming
- Eagerness to learn
- Automobiles

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- Tally

## **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Arabic (Basic)
- Hindi
- Malayalam

# **PROFILE**

+971 55 909 3355

fawazsiddique24@gmail.com

Holding UAE Driver's License